{
    "subject": "resource/Francesco_Maria_Emanuele_Gaetani",
    "predicate": "property/notableworks",
    "object": "Sicilia Nobile",
    "human_readable": "Sicilia Nobile is one of Francesco Maria Emanuele Gaetani's notable works.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9621889591217041,
            "question": "Name a notable work by Francesco Maria Emanuele Gaetani."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8387436270713806,
            "question": "What type of work is Sicilia Nobile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8065483570098877,
            "question": "What other works are attributed to Francesco Maria Emanuele Gaetani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7776534557342529,
            "question": "What is Sicilia Nobile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7393792867660522,
            "question": "Where can one find Sicilia Nobile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6641635894775391,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about Francesco Maria Emanuele Gaetani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6639435291290283,
            "question": "Is Sicilia Nobile considered a significant artwork?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6349790096282959,
            "question": "Who created Sicilia Nobile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5120433568954468,
            "question": "Who would be interested in learning about Sicilia Nobile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4122258126735687,
            "question": "How is Sicilia Nobile perceived by art critics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sicilia Nobile is one of Francesco Maria Emanuele Gaetani's notable works.",
            "html": "dbpedia_95_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who would be interested in learning about Sicilia Nobile?",
            "html": "dbpedia_95_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who created Sicilia Nobile?",
            "html": "dbpedia_95_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sicilia Nobile considered a significant artwork?",
            "html": "dbpedia_95_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_95_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"Della Sicilia nobile\", by Francesco Maria Emanuele E Gaetani, is a replication of a book originally published before 1759. It also mentions that His principal publication was Della Sicilia Nobile, published in five parts between 1754 and 1775, the last part of the appendix published posthumously in 1897."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states that \"His principal publication was Della Sicilia Nobile, published in five parts between 1754 and 1775,\" which indicates that \"Sicilia Nobile\" is indeed one of Francesco Maria Emanuele Gaetani's notable works."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}